

BEN KNOLL

OVERLAND PARK KANSAS

(816) 277 - 9623

■ BKNOLL66@GMAIL.COM

WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/ BENJKNOLL/

SKILLS

NODE.JS REACT.J

EXPRESS.JS MONGO DB

HTML5 MYSOL

CSS3 JAVASQRIPT JQUERY **PROFILE**

I am a full stack web developer, with experience in furniture design. As a maker, I have drafted blueprints and implemented manufacturing processes from start to finish, while maintaining the efficiency and versatility demanded by the project at hand. I believe this unique skill-set partnered with the combination of my creativity, detail orientation, and years of customer service will result in great success within full stack development. Through these experiences I have developed a passion to create clean and responsive user-experiences.

EXPERIENCE

2015 - PRESENT DRVO FURNITURE OWNER | OPERATOR

 Collaborate with clients to imagine, design and create iconic, artisanal furniture.

2013 - 2015 CITY OF LEE'S SUMMIT CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

- Resolved citizen's on-demand questions.
- Created, and maintained, budget tracking spreadsheets.

2012 - 2013 NOODLES & COMPANY SHIFT MANAGER

- Trained and developed new employees.
- Balanced the safe and prepared company deposits.
- Provided fast, quality service to guests.

EDUCATION

2018
UNIVERSITY OF
KANSAS
Fullstack Flex Program

2015
CENTER FOR
FURNITURE
CRAFTSMANSHIP
Furniture
Comprehensive

REFERENCES

CAMERON CHAPMAN

TA at University of Kansas (816) 729 - 0339 cameron.c.chapman@gmail.com PAUL YOUMANS

Aviation Product Trainer at Garmi (816) 877 - 3685 paul.youmans@garmin.com

KYLE REITMEIER

Software Engineer at DST (913) 709 - 0582 kylereitmeier@gmail.com